LAUREN MILES

FULL STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Detroit, MI (937) 329-1424 laurenmiles.dev@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

Software Developer with experience creating modern websites, applications, and automations. Works well in collaborative settings to accomplish common goals, bringing creative ideas and solutions to the table. Has a keen eye to detail to ensure work is completed to a high standard. Has experience working in front-end and back-end development.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Tech Elevator, Columbus, OH (Remote) - *Software Developer*

FEB 2022 - MAY 2023

- Contributed to the Platforms and Infrastructure team by maintaining and improving the BootcampOS application by adding new features and addressing support requests made by employees and students
- Architected and developed workflows (using Azure Functions) to automate internal processes resulting in reduced workload for departments

Nationwide Children's Hospital, Columbus, OH (Remote) - *Software Developer*

OCT 2021 - FEB 2022

- Supported the Marketing team by making updates to the main website framework using Sitecore
- Improved main website by ensuring pages and forms met accessibility requirements
- Maintained existing applications by addressing bugs and support requests reported in the ticketing system

KiZAN Technologies, Louisville, KY (Remote) - *Associate Software Developer/Consultant*

JUN 2020 - OCT 2021

- Contributed to the Custom Application Development team by creating custom applications for clients using Microsoft technologies
- Worked directly with clients to address any feature or support requests
- Exceeded career goals by being utilized as a full time developer within 2 months of employment

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- C#
- .NET
- TypeScript
- JavaScript
- Node.js
- Next.js
- React
- Microsoft Azure
- SQL

EDUCATION

Tech Elevator, Columbus, OH

APR 2020

Attended a 14 week .NET coding bootcamp learning how to create web-based software using C#.

CERTIFICATIONS

Microsoft Azure Fundamentals (AZ-900)

SEP 2020

Demonstrated foundational level knowledge of cloud services and how those services are provided with Microsoft Azure.

LINKS

- GitHub
- LinkedIn
- Portfolio